iridegear.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy

**What** ****is our Privacy Policy****?  
****Your privacy is important to us and we shall not miss out on this opportunity to win your trust.****

We shall therefore only collect information where it is necessary for us to do so and we will only collect information if it is relevant to our dealings with you. We will only keep your information for as long as we are either required to by law or as is relevant for the purposes for which it was collected.

We will only use the details provided by you to us in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy. However you should take note that the information and privacy practices of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we provide hyperlinks, may be different from ours. Our privacy policy is subject to change, to make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically on our site. Though we do everything we reasonably can to comply with the privacy laws of other countries but cannot and do not warrant that we completely do. 

We may at certain times make chat rooms, forums, instant messenger and message boards and other services available to you. Please understand that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when disclosing your personal information to anyone. The Policy does not apply to the procedures and practices followed by entities that are not managed, owned or controlled by bikebasix.com or to the people that are not engaged, employed or managed by bikebasix.com

* * *

**How** ******do we use the data collected from you******?

###  Data that we collect from you includes (but not limited to)

i. User Information example: gender, marital status, age, preferences, likes and dislikes, income, lifestyle levels, contact details, usernames, passwords, email addresses and other security-related information; In the case of Facebook aligned services (if so opted by you), publicly available information of your friends, their likes and dislikes, etc.  
ii. Financial Information example: account history with us including (without limitation) all billing information and communications, Transactional history (other than banking details) about your e-commerce activities, payment history etc. We maintain this in encrypted form on secure servers.  
iii. Internet Related Information example: IP address, browser type, browser language, date and time of request, URLs of websites, which you visit and from which you request downloads, web request, Content, information about your correspondents, and the destination/origin of communications between you and any other person using our Services, Data either created by you or by a third party and which you wish to store on our servers such as image files, documents etc.

###  Data collected is used by us

i. To process your order (product selection – payment – delivery) and keep you updated about the progress of your order. Payments that you make through the Site will be processed by our company Bike Basix Apparel Private Limited, a company registered in India.  
ii. To manage our relationship and provide better services to you and to suggest products that you might like on our website.  
iii. To manage the Site, detect any fraud or Site abuses, send you information relevant to the Site or our products, and in case we have any queries.  
iv. To send you other information about us, our products and promotions and anything relating to other companies in our group or our business partners. If you would prefer not to receive any of this additional information as detailed above please click the “unsubscribe” link in any email that we send to you. Within 7 working days of receipt of your instruction it will be processed. In case your instruction is unclear we will contact you for clarification.  
v. We may also share your data with our franchisor, to sell products to you, directly or indirectly.  
vi. To monitor your use of our Services for the purposes of ensuring compliance with our Terms of Service.  
vii. To compile statistical and demographical profiles for our business activities and to customise our Services to you. While we are entitled to use such information about you for our own internal business purposes without limitation, we will only disclose it in an aggregated form which is not capable of being used or interpreted in such a manner as to identify you. We may use such aggregate data, in our sole discretion and without any compensation to you, for any legitimate purpose including (without limitation) the commercial sale thereof to third parties.  
viii. To use our referral service to tell a friend about our website, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the website. We store this information and the information is used for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.  
ix.  The acceptance of cookies is not a requirement for visiting the Site.  
"Cookies" are are tiny text files used to store user preferences and to track user trends, so that we can provide you with more customised information when you return to our website. We only use cookies for your convenience in using the Site, for example to remember who you are when you want to amend your shopping cart without having to re-enter your email address. If you do accept a "cookie", you thereby agree to our use of any Personal Information collected by us using that Cookie.  
The advertisers on our site may collect anonymous traffic information from their own assigned cookies to your browser; they would not be governed by our privacy policy.

x.   **General Exception**  
If we are required to intercept, disclose, monitor and/or store your Personal Information: (a) by law; (b) to conduct our business; (c) to secure our systems; or (d) to enforce our own rights, we will do so in the manner as prescribed by law.  
Such interception, disclosure, monitoring and storage may take place without your knowledge. In that case, we will not be liable to you or any third party for any damages howsoever arising as such. To ensure that the security and integrity of our Services are safeguarded, we may monitor your Personal Information. This monitoring may include (without limitation) the filtering of incoming and outgoing electronic data messages to identify, limit and/or prevent the transmission of spam, viruses and/or unlawful, defamatory, obscene or otherwise undesirable material or content. We may require the information provided by you for us to deal with special circumstances such as compliance with subpoenas, court orders, requests/order from legal authorities or law enforcement agencies requiring such disclosure. We may under certain circumstances procure an element of the Services from a third party service provider. To the extent that it may be necessary, and solely for the purposes of providing the Service to you, you agree that we may disclose to such third party any of your Personal Information that may be necessary for the procurement of services from the third party.

Your actual order details may be stored with us and you may access this information by logging into your account on the Site. We cannot assume any liability for misuse of passwords unless this misuse is our fault. You undertake to treat the personal access data confidentially and not make it available to unauthorized third parties.

Upon request, we will remove / block your personally identifiable information from our database, thereby cancelling your registration. However, your information may remain stored in archive on our servers even after the deletion or the termination of your account.

We will only disclose your Personal Information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If we want to use it for any other purpose, we will obtain your prior written consent. Any information provided in any open, public environment or forum including (but not limited to) any blog, community or discussion board, is not confidential, does not constitute Personal Information, and is not subject to protection under Privacy Policy. We request you to use your discretion while entering data in such public environments, as this is at your own risk. We are not liable to you or any third party for any damages that you or any third party may suffer howsoever arising from your disclosure of Personal Information in any public environment. All disputes would be handled by Ahmadabad courts.
